Hi!  I’m reading section 4 of your paper now!  You said I should skip the other sections, so I did.  I have all the comments!  Yaaaaayyy   sorry I have a lot to say here, but you’ve got a good start and it won’t be too hard to adjust what you’ve got.

First, here is some basic advice on how to refer to figures.

- You need to refer to them in order.  You can’t first refer to figure 3 and then figure 2.  Where is figure 1?   Do you refer to figure 1 at all?  If not, why is it there?  

- When you mention a figure, you need to describe it in detail before you go on.  “Figure 2 depicts Blah vs. Thing, where the colored lines indicate This Thing and That Thing, and the dashed and dotted lines refer to Whatever and However.  From this Figure we can see that Your Mom correlates with Your Dad, indicating that You Exist.”  Or something.  This is totally boring, but you can’t assume that people are going to understand your figure by glancing at it (especially if it’s on another page, which is common).  You should also assume that they will not read the caption.  Your caption should repeat this info, but more briefly.  

- pie charts are frowned upon in the professional sciences, you might need to make stacked bar plots for the paper.  Sorry.

- once you have described a type of plot (colored and solid/dashed lines)  you don’t really need to do it again.  You can say “line styles are as in Figure X” where X is a figure you’ve already talked about in detail.  i.e. for the h277 section you can skip the dashed/colored descriptions.

More specific thoughts:

Page 15, end of first paragraph.  You make the great statement that your results are contrary to mine, cool!  What does that mean?  Why is it significant? You need more here on the fact that this is a big deal.  The way you have it now makes it sound kind of ho-hum.  

End of section 4.1 - I don’t see any data that backs up your conclusion here at all.  The lowest angular momentum gas is the cold gas, the merger gas isn’t lowest so it’s not clear why you claim that the merger gas is preferred.  I don’t think we’ve proven that at all actually, we need to do more analysis to show it (i.e. analyzing specifically the gas which enters during that particular merger, which you had been doing for a while but stopped).

The phrase “merger-gained” is awkward, why not call it clumpy?

Supernova contamination of shocked gas to h277 - what evidence do we have for this?  Have you looked at it?  What does this mean?

In general, some more explanation of what your conclusions *mean* is important.  You say at the end of 4.2  "the h277 galaxy accretes gas with lower angular momentum than that of its SMBH “  so what?  What is the significance of this?  Imagine if you were first-year Bridge Student Nicole, in September when you’re just starting your work.  You’d be like “why is the angular momentum lower?  what does that mean?  Why should I care about the angular momentum at all?  Why is it important?  Why is she even plotting it?  What question is she trying to answer with this plot?”  Picture yourself 1.5 years ago and refocus your thoughts on this section of the paper.  
￼
